man that this isn't some of the wildest
stuff that I've already put together
and with everything going on and all the
scops.
Look what we have going on now with
Erica France Va.
actually take a listen to the director
Clayton himself describe a bit about
what this was intended to be about. I
say intended because when you start
reading the comments in the Kickstarter
campaign, you realize they never
deliver. They promised to deliver it in
2013. That didn't happen. Uh here is the
director Clayton Hogan speaking about
this movie.
>> You guys just saw there was a visual
pitch to really give you a feel for the
atmosphere. As far as concept goes, we
really developed it around a number of
questions that we were asking ourselves.
Now, these questions range from anything
from how can we manipulate someone's
senses enough so that they believe a
false reality when in reality something
else is going on entirely or even how
can someone like the class geek pirate
and steal say the varsity quarterback's
you know knowledge and skill set or even
more so how can the knowledge and skill
set of a Navy Seal be copied and you
know transferred to somebody else
>> and this concept became possible when we
really pushed the boundary on what's
called nanotechnology
>> tiny little microscope opic machines
that carry out their function on an
atomic level. Now with nanotechnology,
we were able to create this plausible
and you know believable mindbending and
reality bending concept that is grounded
in you know developing physics theories
out there in developing science. So
really the question you should ask
yourself is what happens in a world
where the brain is a hard drive, your
eyes become video cameras and knowledge
is not learned so much it is just
programs that are installed onto you.
>> Wow.
Yeah. So, that's not going to help
matters any in the world of us
conspiracy theorists [laughter] trying
to think that that's what happening.
>> That's definitely what's happening right
now, man.
>> Walking around computer program,
>> man. I'm telling you, like I did a deep
dive on
nanotechnology
and
I had to make a new account,
you know, they didn't they didn't like
that. And this one probably won't make
it either.
But uh wow, man. Like that's scary
because uh
yeah, there are really people out there
that's uh uh getting this stuff put in
them.
It's true. Yeah. And it's happening. And
they're doing it with our Wi-Fi boxes,
man.
So
pay attention.